Magical Girl Nicolara!
Nicolara
Magical Girl
(ｽﾊﾟﾎﾞｰﾝ)ﾀｲﾑｾｰﾙ！
Time for a flash sale!
(ﾆｺﾗﾗ)あなたの怒り 星空の彼方へ
笑い飛ばしてあげる！
I'm gonna send your wrath soaring beyond the stars in the sky!
ｽﾏｲﾙ～ ﾊﾘｹｰﾝ！
Smile...
Hurricane!
ﾆｺ～！
Nico!
本日は閉店しました～！
Sorry, but we're closed for today!
きゃはっ！
(はじける音)
(まひろ)いいな～ 今年の日ｱｻ｡
The current Sunday morning lineup is so hype.
５人から１人になって
不安だったけど
I was worried about them ditching the team-of-five formula,
これはこれで悪くない｡
but focusing on one character isn't all that bad.
いや いい！ むしろ ﾑﾑﾑ…｡
(ﾘﾓｺﾝの音)
Actually, no! It's great!
(ﾆｺﾗﾗ)ﾊﾋﾟﾈｽ ﾌﾙ ﾌｨｰﾙﾄﾞ！
Happiness Full Field!
～
ｱﾊｯ う～ん…｡
ｷｬﾊｯ！
うおお～！ うん よし！
Okay!
う～ん…｡
んっ！ ﾌﾝｯ！
ｽﾏｲﾙ～！
Smile...
ﾊﾘｹｰﾝ！ あっ…｡
Hurricane!
(ｾﾐの声)
Huh?
は…｡
(みはり)｢ぐ ぐぇ～ やられた～｣｡
C-Curses!
やめて！ そっとしといて！
You got me!
Stop it! Leave me alone!
What's here is gone
What's gone is here
Today a cucumber, tomorrow a clam
Gotta check my trousers, trance, trance, trance
What's his is gone
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
What's hers is here
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
My pronouns are in shambles!
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Sister
Your
Now
I'm
ONIMAI:
Gone are the days of making wagies seethe
oyama Mahiro
(Bye-bye alright! I'm still unemployable!)
oyama Mihari
Without balls I just can't get up for it
(Scratch that, grow a pair! I won't stand for this!)
Ah, having peered into a queer new world
I've been bewitched by its siren song
I dove right in and the water's great
Cute outfits, makeup galore, and hairstyles aplenty
The world of women is calling my name
Wait, I'm a dude! Or am I?
(Are!)
(Who!)
Some part of my identity is crumbling
(It's me!)
Leading to a newborn sense of wonder
As an unknown sensation pervades my psyche
Awaken, my inner cute girl!
With proper stimulation comes a happy ending?
What's here is gone
What's gone is here
Today a cucumber, tomorrow a clam
Gotta check my trousers, trance, trance, trance
What's his is gone
What's hers is here
My manhood's in total shambles!
#fdfdfc Mahiro's New Friend
You've become a real little girl,
right down to your interests.
The Sunday morning block is for all men of culture!
むう～｡
うっ ぐっ… く…｡
お兄ちゃん… とうとう趣味まで
女児そのものに…｡
I'm afraid I must take my leave.
日ｱｻは紳士のたしなみだ！
おわあ！
はあ…｡
Huh?
B-But whatever for, Mihari?!
Have I disappointed you in some way?!
おいとまを いただきます｡
Don't be silly.
ほぇ…｡
Anyway, it was just a formality.
な なぜだ みはり！
ｵﾚに何か至らぬところが？
I'm at a major turning point in my research,
so I'll most likely be staying over at school tonight.
よく言うわ｡
Do you think you can take care of things at home for me?
まぁ 今のは言葉のあやで｡
B-But—
ちょっと研究が山場でね
But of course!
一晩 大学に
泊まりこみになりそうなの｡
I wouldn't have it any other way!
お留守番… できるかな？
You're talking to a pro home security officer, remember?!
な な…｡
な～んだぁ～｡
Oh, is that right?
それなら むしろ望むところだ！
こちとら自宅警備のﾌﾟﾛだぞ！
You'll have to make yourself dinner, all right?
ﾌﾟﾛねぇ～｡
I-I'll just get something from the corner store...
(ｾﾐの声)
ご飯 自分で用意してね｡
And don't forget the housework!
うっ｡ こ ｺﾝﾋﾞﾆなら たぶん…｡
That I cannot promise!
Are you sure you'll be okay?
I'll be fine! Quit worrying, will ya?
お掃除もお願いね｡
それは約束しかねる｡
I have a bad feeling...
See you tomorrow!
あ…｡
ﾎﾝﾄに大丈夫？
Yep, yep!
大丈夫だって～ しつこいなぁ｡
不安だな～｡
行ってきま～す｡
はいは～い｡
Freedom!
Time to loaf around to my heart's content!
ん…｡
ｴﾍｯ…｡
自由だ～！
Maybe I should get changed first.
思う存分 だらけるぞ～！
NEET
This brings back memories!
どわぁ～！
So loose and baggy!
はぁ～ あ まずは着替えるか｡
Wait! What am I getting all excited about?
わあ～ なつかしい この感じ～！
ﾌﾞｶﾌﾞｶだ～！ ﾜﾊﾊﾊﾊ！
I guess I could play a game or something.
って なに喜んでんだ！
GUTS
とりあえず ｹﾞｰﾑでもするか～｡
(ｹﾞｰﾑ音)
Not feeling it right now for some reason.
ﾌﾌ～｡
(ｹﾞｰﾑ音)
ん…｡
ん～｡
Maybe I'll read manga instead.
はあ～ どうも身が入らん…｡
ん～｡
ﾏﾝｶﾞでも読むか…｡
(ｾﾐの声)
I just can't focus on any of it.
Come to think of it, ever since I got this new body,
Mihari's been there watching over me in some way or another.
あ ふわああ～｡
な～んか 全然頭に入ってこない｡
そういや この身体になってから
なんだかんだで
いつもみはりが そばにいたっけ｡
Pro Sumo Wrestling
Shusse Ozumo
～
We even play games together now and then.{there was that screenshot of the game title screen just now, and we see them playing it later on. So I think that's probably what she is musing about.}
No, wait! Stop it!
I'm making it sound like I'm lonely or something!
That's it! I need food!
最近は たまに一緒に遊んだり…｡
And I'm gonna go all out!
むわあ～！ 違う違う！
Whoa!
これじゃあ
寂しいみたいじゃないか！
It's a feast!
もうﾒｼだ ﾒｼ！ 豪華にいくぞ～！
おおぉ～！
A feasht fit for a king!
うたげだ～！
ﾃﾞﾍ～！
And ish all for me!
ああ～むっ！
Pizha shure ish nice every oncsh in a while!
まさに きぞく～！ ﾌﾌﾌｯ！
The oiler the becher!
ぜ～んぶ ひとりじめだあ！
Wai— Water— Mihari—!
ん～ はむ！
たまに食べるとうまいよな～｡
こってり ぎとぎと 最高～！
うぶっ！ ちょ 水…｡
みはりぃ～｡
あ…｡
ん…｡
(水を飲む音)
I think I'm full.
ん…｡
(虫の鳴き声)
Guess I'll go take a bath and head to bed.
腹 いっぱいだな…｡
風呂でも入って
さっさと寝よう…｡
I'm home!
～
Onii-chan?
(鳥のさえずり)
ただいま～｡
You awake?
はぁ～ お兄ちゃ～ん？
(ﾉｯｸ)
You went to bed without drying your hair, didn't you?
起きてる～？
Honestly. I knew you'd be hopeless without me.
あ～ 頭乾かさずに寝たわね｡
やっぱり
まだ私が見てないとﾀﾞﾒね｡
There! That's much bette—
～
Wh-What's wrong? What happened?
N-Nothing!
ほ～ら かわいくなった… わっ！
Dummy.
な なに!? どうしたの!?
う うっさい！
ONIMAI
Onimai.
ﾊﾞｶ…｡
あ あ…｡
ONIMAI
Onimai.
Mihari! Slow down!
～
Oh, Onii-chan... So this is your weak spot, huh?
あ うはぁ…｡
みはり それはだめぇ…｡
Stop! I'm near the edge!
へぇ～ お兄ちゃん
ここが弱いんだ…｡
I'm almost there!
わ うわああ…｡
あぁ… そんなぁ…｡
Yay! I win!
ぐぅ… 出るぅ…｡
And I'm out.
出ちゃう～！
Go pick up the groceries like we promised, okay?
どうだ！
It's the supermarket across from the station.
いえ～い！ 私の勝ち～！
出ちゃった…｡
I wrote a list of everything we need.
Grrr...
う ぐぅ…｡
じゃあ 約束どおり おつかいね｡
Hmph!
You can buy yourself a treat with the change, if you'd like.
駅前のｽｰﾊﾟｰまで｡
買うものは
ここにﾒﾓしてあるから｡
I'm not a child!
Fine, I'll do it.
う… うぬぬぬ…｡ ﾌﾝｯ！
I'm a man of my word, after all.
おつりでお菓子買ってもいいよ～｡
子どもか！
I-I'll be right back...
しかたない…
男に二言はないからな｡
ﾌﾌｯ｡
You got this!
い 行ってくるぅ…｡
頑張って～！
うう ううぅ…｡
ﾌｯ…｡
～
Looks like he's slowly getting used to going out.
He's even started helping around the house more,
ever since he helped me through that cold.
ﾜﾝｯ！
う うえぇ！
《お兄ちゃん だんだん外にも
慣れてきたみたい｡
He might be able to go back to a normal life soon.
風邪のとき以来
And then one day, he'll meet a great guy and...
お手伝いも少しだけ
してくれるようになったし》
Oh, darling...
これは社会復帰も近いかも…｡
I'm so happy.
そしていつか
いいお婿さんを見つけて…｡
Okay, not likely.
But one can dream.
ﾀﾞｰﾘﾝ 幸せ…｡
LIKE
ん～
な～んて そりゃないか～｡
Mommy, I want hamburger steak for dinner!
(ざわめき)
You have to ask nicely, dear.
I can't do this!
う～ わあ～｡
The corner store was bad enough!
There are way too many people here!
おかあさん 今夜ﾊﾝﾊﾞｰｸﾞ！
わがまま言っちゃ いけません｡
N-No! I can't just cower here like a child!
やっぱ無理～！
I proved my capable-big-brotherness
when Mihari was ill, didn't I?!
近所のｺﾝﾋﾞﾆならまだしも
さすがに人が多すぎる！
し しかし
ここで怖気づいてどうする！
Excuse me...
この前
みはりの看病をしてやって
Y—
Yes?!
せっかく
兄の威厳が回復したってのに…｡
(もみじ)あの～｡
はっ！
E-E-E-Err...
ひゃ ひゃい！
(もみじ)あ…｡
Are you okay? Do you feel sick?
Huh?
(おびえる声)
ﾍﾍ…｡
うわあ あばばば…｡
大丈夫？ 体調悪いの？
えっ…｡
You don't seem to have a fever.
Um...
If you need help, I'd be happy to lend a hand.
ひゃあ！
ん ん…｡
熱はないね えっと…｡
何か困ってるなら 手伝うけど…｡
Sorry about this.
あ… うううぅ～｡
Don't be silly! It's my pleasure.
ああ…｡
あっ｡
I can't believe I dragged this poor boy into this.
なんか ごめんね～｡
I'm not huge on big crowds myself.
ううん 全然！
役に立ててよかったよ～｡
So what did you need to get?
U-Uh, I have a list...
見知らぬ少年に
泣きついてしまった…｡
Beef, sliced pork
Potatoes
Carrots
Onions
Shirataki noodles
Beef, sliced pork, potatoes, carrots, onions, and shirataki noodles.
たしかに 人ごみは嫌だよね～｡
それで なに買うの？
え えと… ﾒﾓが…｡
For nikujaga stew, right?
(もみじ)牛肉
豚肉のこまぎれ
Are you okay with the cheaper meat?
じゃがいも
にんじん
I'm not sure.
たまねぎ しらたき…
肉じゃがかな～？
Let's see how much you have,
and we can go from there.
May Queen Potatoes
お肉は安いのでいいの？
さあ～？
じゃあ予算見て 考えようか！
They all look the same to me.
You wanna look for ones that are smooth and don't have any bruising.
For carrots, I heard the deeper the color and smaller the stem, the better.
ん～ どれも同じに見える…｡
あんまりﾃﾞｺﾎﾞｺしてなくて
ｼﾜのないものがいいよ｡
You're so knowledgeable!
You think so?
にんじんは色濃くて
芯が小さいと おいしいんだって｡
Ahh... What a nice guy.
たのもし～！
そう～？
Look, aren't those two cute?
I wonder if they're a couple.
Stop talking about strangers like that.
《はあ～ なんか いいﾔﾂだな～》
A-A couple?!
(らいか)見て見て かわい～｡
んっ？
O-Oh, right. I'm a girl right now.
(らいか)あの子たち ｶｯﾌﾟﾙかな～？
(ひより)やめなよ そういうの…｡
No, but still! You can't just—
か ｶｯﾌﾟﾙぅ～!? はっ！
Is something wrong?
そ そっか… ｵﾚ 今 女の子だし…｡
Uh... Wait a sec.
いやいや
だからって そんな… ああ～｡
Why am I so flustered?
どうしたの？
ひやぁ！ うぅ｡
Are you feeling okay?
I-It's not like that!
あ あれ!? なんだこの気持ち…｡
There's been a big mistake here!
あ あぇ…｡
Have a nice day!
大丈夫？
ち ちが～う！
これは何かの間違いだ～ ぐぅ～！
えっ!?
My body had a mind of its own for a second there.
I'm glad you were able to get everything!
ありがとうございました～｡
Y-Yeah! Thanks!
W-Well, Imma head— I-I'll be heading home now...
危うく攻略されるところだった…｡
ちゃんと買えたね！
う うん… ありがと…｡
Sorry, gimme one sec.
そ それじゃあ ｵﾚ
わ わたしはこれで…｡
Hello?
I'm in front of the supermarket with a friend.
Friend...
あ ごめん ちょっと待って！
Oh! There you are!
もしもし～ 今ｽｰﾊﾟｰの前｡
Momiji!
友達と一緒！
ともだち…｡
Kaede-chan?!
Onee-chan!
(足音)
Wait, you're friends with Mahiro-chan?
(かえで)あっ いたいた～！
(もみじ/まひろ)んっ？
Where did you guys meet?
(かえで)もみじ～！
"Onee-chan"?!
お姉ちゃん！
かえでちゃん!? んっ？
Come to think of it, she did say she had a little sister, didn't she?
あれ 友達って まひろちゃん？
どこで仲よくなったの？
お お姉ちゃん!?
"Little sister"?
You're a girl?!
《そういえば かえでちゃん
妹がいるって言ってたっけ…》
You didn't know? Do I really look that boyish?
えっ!?
いもうと？
You could at least put on a skirt.
女の子!?
But I'm more comfortable in pants!
やっぱり？
そんなに男っぽいかな…｡
Aww...
Give it a rest, okay?
Thank goodness... She's a girl.
ﾌｯ ﾌﾌｯ｡
うわ…｡
You're so sheepish sometimes.
せめてｽｶｰﾄにすればいいのに～｡
That was a close one.
ｽﾞﾎﾞﾝのほうが 楽なんだもん！
え～｡
もういいから～！
そうか… 女の子…｡
Oh!
よかったあ～｡
(もみじ/かえで)んっ？
You mean Momiji-chan?
She'd be in middle school now, I think.
She's a good kid, isn't she?
Yeah...
She had me questioning myself for a minute there.
ああ～！
もみじちゃんね 中学生だっけ？
しっかりしてるよね～｡
Y-You're into little girls?!
うん 危うく道を踏み外すかと…｡
No, that's not what I meant!
ん… うえぇ!?
Besides, I'm technically the same age as her now, aren't I?
Wait... Does that make me a lesbian?
お お兄ちゃんのﾛﾘｺﾝ！
え いや
そういう意味じゃなくて！
っていうか
今はｵﾚも見た目JCだろ！
ONIMAI
Onimai.
Oyama
んっ？
それじゃあ これは百合なのか？
Come in, come in!
Thanks for having us!
う…｡
Sorry about this.
I know you must be busy.
いらっしゃ～い！
(かえで/もみじ)お邪魔しま～す｡
Nonsense, it's fine!
Wait a sec! Hey, Kaede-chan!
(かえで)ごめんね～
みはり 忙しいのに｡
Oh! Hi, Mahiro-chan!
Sorry to bother you guys.
いいって いいって～｡
And this is...?
Hello! Nice to see you again!
あれ～ かえでちゃん！
あっ まひろちゃん！
Who?
お邪魔してま～す｡
それと…｡
I-It's Momiji!
We met the other day, remember?!
こんにちは お邪魔してます｡
S-Sorry, it's just...
You're wearing a skirt today,
so I didn't recognize you, you know?
だれ…｡
えっ も もみじだよ～！
この前 会ったでしょ～！
うっ！
It's my school uniform.
い いや～ ほら！
We came straight here from school.
今日はｽｶｰﾄだし
なんか雰囲気ちがうから～！
Sorry we didn't tell you.
She just insisted on tagging along.
ﾍﾍﾍﾍ ﾍﾍ…｡
制服だもん… 学校帰りなの｡
Why not? May as well if you are!
ふぅ｡
あ…｡
急にごめんね～｡
I'm here to study for a test, you know?
一緒に来るってきかなくって～｡
だって せっかくだし！
Honestly.
You're hopeless.
お姉ちゃん
これからﾃｽﾄ勉強するんだよ～？
Sorry, Mahiro-chan.
うぅ… ん…｡
Do you mind playing with Momiji up in your room?
もう しかたないな～！
Wha? M-My room?
ごめんね～ まひろちゃん｡
Just gimme one sec!
お部屋で
もみじと遊んであげてくれない？
ん…｡
えっ!? お お部屋って…｡
ちょっと 待ってて！
でぇ！ ﾍｪ ﾍｪ ﾍｪ…｡
Mahiro
～
C-Come in...
Thank you!
ふん！
～
Wow!
Being alone in my room with a girl was not on today's agenda!
ど どうぞ～｡
お邪魔しま～す｡
What do you even do in this situation?!
(もみじ)へぇ～｡
Your room's more boyish than I thought it was gonna be.
You have so many game consoles!
自分の部屋で
突然 女の子と２人きり…｡
Y-You think so?
いったい 何をして遊べと…｡
I can't let her look around too much!
意外と男の子っぽい部屋だね｡
Th-Think of something to talk about! Anything!
ｹﾞｰﾑ機とか いっぱい！
そ そう？
By the way, Mahiro-chan.
《あんまり見られるとまずい…｡
What's thi—?
と とにかく
ここは何か話題を…》
Oh! That's right!
Do you hate skirts, Momiji?
U-Um... I wouldn't go that far.
Huh?
ところで まひろちゃん
これって…｡
But skirts feel so drafty, right?
ああ～ そうだ～！
もみじは ｽｶｰﾄ嫌いなの？
へっ？
It feels a little pointless.
え あ ん～ 嫌いっていうか
ｽｶｰﾄって 足元ｽｰｽｰしない？
I-I-I feel that!
They don't really suit me anyway.
なんか頼りなくって…｡
What? That's not true!
You look pretty cute to me.
わ わわ わかる～！
C-Cu...
それに そもそも似合わないし…｡
N-No way! You look ten times cuter than I do!
え～ なんで？
普通にかわいいと思うけど～｡
Wait, wha...?!
か かわ!?
うぅ～ そ そんなの！
No, no, no! No way!
Well, actually, I do look pretty cute...
絶対 絶対
まひろちゃんのがかわいいし～！
But we're not talking about me!
ううえぇ～？
が うえぇ！
So you admit it, huh?
いや いやいやいや～！
まぁ たしかに
かわいいかもだけど…｡
って これはちがくて！
ﾌﾌﾌﾌ…｡
認めたな～！
Time for punishment!
あ あわわわ…｡
Stop, stop, stop! Stop it!
Wait, what? Huh?
Take this, and that!
ｷｬﾊﾊﾊ！
What's happening?
Is this how girls interact with each other?
I'm not done yet!
こうしてやる～！
ややや あぁ やめてぇ～！
Tickle, tickle, tickle!
N-No more!
《あえ えっ？ なにこれぇ…｡
女の子同士って こうなのか？》
うへぇ あ あもう だめぇ～！
あぁ～！
あっ！
I'm sorry! I took it too far!
ぐえっ！
う ううぅ…｡
うわ～！ やりすぎた ごめん～！
A-Anyway...
I'm sure if you give it some time,
you'll get used to them.
うぅ…｡
Plus, you might feel better if you wore tights underneath.
ん… ん～｡
G-Got it.
ま まぁ ｽｶｰﾄなんて
そのうち慣れるって～｡
I'm so sorry about your manga, Mahiro-chan!
They're all over the floor...
あとはﾀｲﾂ履くと 違うと思うよ｡
Milkpie
そ そっか…｡
I-I-I-I-Is this—?
あ ごめんね
まひろちゃんの漫画…｡
Don't look at that!
たくさん散らかしちゃって…｡
ひゃうっ！
(あえぎ声)
こここ これって…｡
うわあ～！ 見ちゃﾀﾞﾒ～！
Mahiro-chan?
Um... Is that...
ううぅ うう…｡
I-Is that a... dirty...
This is... Um, you know?
まひろちゃん…
あの それって…｡
そ それって えっちな…｡
うぐっ！
This is my brother's!
Your brother's?
Uh...
これは… ええ～っと その…｡
Y-Yeah. Um... Err...
う… これはお兄ちゃんの！
This used to be my big brother's room, you see?
お兄ちゃん？
うっ！
I-I'm just... using it for the time being.
あ あの… あの えっと…｡
う… こ ここは！
もともとお兄ちゃんの部屋で…｡
Oh! He got into a good college,
so he's living on his own far away from home.
そのまま お… 私が使ってて…｡
So your brother's into that kind of stuff, huh?
あっ！ お兄ちゃんは
いい大学に通ってて…｡
今は
遠くで一人暮らしなんだけど…｡
うぅ…｡
そういうのが好きな
お兄さんなんだ…｡
I-I couldn't just throw out all his stuff.
どぅわ！
So I just kept everything the way he left it.
I know it's weird, but...
(すすり泣く声)
They remind me of him...
か 勝手に捨てちゃ悪いから
全部そのままにしてあるの…｡
I see...
That makes sense.
こんなのでも
But still...
思い出の 品だから…｡
You really shouldn't have these lying around!
そっか… なるほどね｡
Wha?
Let's at least put the dirty ones away somewhere!
でも んん…｡
I'll help!
Wha?
さすがに これはよくないよ！
What?!
Uh... Hold on...
ふぇ…｡
Look, there's a box right over there.
せめて えっちな本は片づけよ！
Making This
Sassy Babe Mine
私も手伝うから！
えっ!?
えっ あの…｡
ちょうどいい箱があるね｡
A Peach-Colored Life
Raising My Own Elves
The Sexy Fox Spirit
Super Sexy Cooking
Tightly Bound
Complex 3P
んん～｡
Um... Could we at least sort them by genre?
はっ！ ううぅ…｡
～
あ… できればｼﾞｬﾝﾙごとに…｡
That should do it.
あ… うぅ…｡
Farewell, my comrades...
～
Though I guess we're not throwing them out,
so it's not the end of the world.
ふぅ こんなもんかな｡
Now to put this in the closet.
さらば 我が戦友たち…｡
でも捨てるってわけじゃないし
別にいいか～｡
Be careful, it's heavy!
I got it!
あとはこれをｸﾛｰｾﾞｯﾄに っと…｡
I'll help you!
ん…｡
あっ｡
気をつけて重いよ～｡
うん…｡
手伝う！ うぅ！ う…｡
Ow, ow, ouch...
っと ひえ…｡
(もみじ)う うわ…｡
Sorry! Are you all right?
(まひろ/もみじ)うわあ～！
(倒れる音)
あ いたた…｡
ごめんね 大丈夫？ はっ！
あ あ…｡
What happened?!
I heard a really big thud just now!
は はうぅ…｡
(走る足音)
Um...
どうしたの!?
またすごい音したけど!?
んっ？
I-I swear, Mihari— Onee-chan!
It's not what it looks like!
あの…｡
(まひろ/もみじ)えっ!?
Mahiro-chan, shouldn't she be the one saying that, not you?
ち ちがうぞ みはり…
お姉ちゃん！ 誤解だ～！
Already acting like besties, huh?
まひろちゃん 普通そういうのって
逆じゃない？
ﾌﾌｯ｡
I'm so glad she catches on quick.
もうすっかり仲よしね～｡
あ…｡
Thanks for today!
I'm much more confident about the test now!
ｴﾍﾍ～｡
Good luck!
理解が早くて助かった… ｸﾞｰ！
See you later, Mahiro-chan!
(かえで)今日はありがとう～｡
Y-Yeah!
おかげで いい点とれそう！
ﾃｽﾄ がんばって～！
あ…｡
またね まひろちゃん！
Look at you, making friends!
う うん！
Me making friends with a girl her age is basically a crime!
～
But you're around the same age as her now.
Hmm, I guess.
お友達できて よかったじゃ～ん｡
More importantly...
Hmm?
JCとお友達って 犯罪っぽいぞ！
She touched my boobs.
お兄ちゃんだって JCじゃない｡
むぅ… そうか｡
それはともかく…｡
んっ？
So, what did you guys do together?
Wha? Oh! Uh...
おっぱい… もまれた…｡
It's a secret!
まひろちゃんと 何して遊んだの？
She seems cool, though, doesn't she?
えっ？ あ～ ん～ 内緒！
With a one-two-three, it's time to play
ん…｡
おもしろい子だな まひろちゃん｡
Come and join us in a secret hideaway
Hey, br- I mean, Mahiro! Wanna try on a maid outfit?
Huh?
No, it's gotta be a bunny-girl costume!
H-Hold on!
Let's go with a dress, we can even match!
Point is, it's time to strip!
Hey! Cut it out!
Noooooooooo!
A genius has at a docile lab rat
(And in the night...)
A single dose, perfection isn't slow!
(Hey, what the heck?)
Cutie acquired, cuddles required
Partner recaptured, hey, let's go!
(Oh, deary me!)
(Time for a show)
Let's have a sleepover, yay, yay, yay!
(And someone's gonna feel like they're the odd one out!)
The girls got a little somethin' goin' on tonight
(Send help, I don't know how to feel)
With a one-two-three, it's time to play
And break the gender barrier
Soon enough your heart's athrob
Time to welcome you into a place you've never known!
(One! Two!)
(It's a bouncy world!)
It's time to reassess! No more stress!
Just submit, surrender, don't obsess!
Girls with itty-bitty bodies can still
Be packed with secrets deep within!
Give your all, have a ball!
Right until the cards'll start to fall!
There's one thing that you really should know:
Girl power makes the world go 'round!
If there's an identity crisis coming on, it can wait another day
(虫の鳴き声)
They were so soft and squishy...
Still rock-solid!
柔らかかった…｡
Illustration: Nakamura Yutaka
Next Episode: Mahiro Discovers Adventure and Social Gatherings
See you next week!!
See you next time!
んっ…｡
かたい…｡